제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
에릭
Eric, you've hardly touched
your breakfast.
아침밥에 손도 안 댔구나
뭔지 몰라서 못 먹겠어요
That's because
I don't know what it is.
이건 그냥..
달걀이랑 다진 고기랑
Well, it's just--
it's eggs and hash...
그리고 약간의
and some...
깜짝 재료란다
surprises.
엄마는 왜 안 드세요?
Mom, why aren't you eating it?
난 원래 아침같은 거 안 먹잖니
Well, I have never been
a breakfast person.
이거 토끼고기에요?
Is this rabbit?
아니
No.
엄마, 아빠가 직장 구하면
이런 개밥 그만 먹어도 돼요?
Mom, if Daddy gets a job,
can we stop eating dog food?
로리, 개밥이라니!
하여간 나도 그렇게 됐으면 좋겠구나
Laurie, it is not dog food.
And, God, I hope so.
어때?
So?
저를 채용하시겠습니까?
Would you hire me?
난 고용할 거예요, 특히 '세상에서
제일 좋은 아빠' 자리라면요
I'd hire you, Daddy, especially
if the position was World's Best Father.
너땜에 내가 아주 환장한다
Oh, you make me sick.
이거 말고기에요?
Is it horse?
말고기 같은 거 아니야!
No, it is not horse.
여보, 당신 공장 문 닫은 후로
좀 우울해 했었잖아요
Honey, now I know you've been just
a little bit blue since the plant closed.
그래서 내가 선물을 준비했어요
So, I got you a present.
짜잔!
Ta-da!
"당신을 고용합니다"
"You're Hired!
"구직을 위한 필수 가이드"
The Essential Guide
For Job Hunting. "
여보, 난 이런 거 필요없어
Kitty, I don't need that.
난 16살 때부터 일을 해 왔고
I've been working
since I was 16.
전쟁에도 두 번이나 참전했고
젠장, 사람들도 죽여봤다고!
I fought in two wars.
Hell, I killed people.
마지못해 했다는 소리는 아니야
I-- I'm not saying
that I didn't enjoy it.
아뇨, 아뇨, 그런게 아니라
난 그냥 격려해 주려고 그런건데
No, no, no, no. I just, I thought
it'd give you a little edge.
격려같은 거 필요없어
난 레드 포먼이야!
I don't need an edge.
I'm Red Forman.
난 숙련돼 있고
성실하고, 근면하다고!
I'm experienced, loyal,
hardworking.
- 그게 바로 임용 능력의 3대 요소에요
- 고맙구나, 아가!
- That's the trifecta of employ ability!
- Well, thanks, sweetie.
- 행운을 빌어요, 여보
- 다녀오세요, 아빠
- Good luck, honey.
- Bye, Daddy!
- 다녀오세요
- 알았다!
- Okay.
- I got it!
이거 혓바닥이다!
It's tongue.
혓바닥 고기야
토퍼 그레이스 (에릭 포먼)
밀라 커니스 (재키 벅하트)
애쉬튼 커쳐 (마이클 켈소)
대니 메스털슨 (스티븐 하이드)
로라 프레폰 (도나 핀씨오티)
윌머 발더라마 (페즈)
데브라 조 러프 (키티 포먼)
커트우드 스미스 (레드 포먼)
타냐 로버츠 (미지 핀씨오티)
돈 스탁 (밥 핀씨오티)
리사 로빈 켈리 (로리 포먼)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 오흥민(echem@nate)
제작지원 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
번역 : 조영희(brunette@nate)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 오흥민(echem@nate)
제작지원 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
2x03 The Velvet Rope
Oct 12, 1999 on FOX
좋아, 공식적으로 밝히겠어
All right, it's official.
우리 부모님 완전 변태들이야!
My parents are freaks!
그래도 내 남자친구 할 사람?
Which one of you
is my boyfriend again?
그래, 너
Right, it's you.
넌 오늘밤 나를 이 구린 동네에서
탈출시켜야 돼
You're taking me out
of this stinkin' town tonight!
잠깐, 잠깐만, 도나
Wait, wait, wait. Donna,
페즈가 왜 팬티만 입고 있는지
알고 싶지 않아?
don't you wanna
know why Fez is in his undies?
아니
No.
진짜 말도 안되는 얘기야
It is a really crazy story.
오! 그래?
Oh. Oh, you know what?
I'll tell you a crazy story.
진짜 말도 안되는 얘기가
뭔지 말해주지
한 4분쯤 전에 있었던 일이야..
It all started like
four minutes ago.
세상에, 지금 뭐하고 계시는 거예요?
Oh, good God.
What are you guys doing now?
요가, 네 아빠의 챠크라를
정렬시켜 주고 있단다
Yoga. I'm trying to align
your father's chakras.
난 그 빌어먹을 것이
흐트러져 있는 줄도 몰랐단다
I didn't even know the damn things
were out of whack.
좀 평범해 지시면 안 돼요?
Why can't you guys be normal?
도나, 네 부정적인 기운이
우리 정기를 해치고 있구나
Donna, your negativity is bruising
our auras. Please leave.
나가 주겠니?
- 기꺼이요!
- 아 참, 애야
- Gladly.
- Oh, and, honey.
우리 탄트라 섹스도 해볼 거야
We're also exploring tantric sex.
그러니까 오늘밤 우리방에서
이상한 소리가 들려도 놀라지..
So, if you hear any strange noises coming from
Mommy and Daddy's bedroom tonight--
우웩!
Ew!
왜 맨날 이렇게
절 맛이 가게 하시는데요?
Why must you guys
freak me out on a daily basis?
두분 벌거벗은 거 상상하기 싫어요
저 나갈 거예요
I don't want to picture you naked.
And I'm leaving now.
영원히
Forever.
저런!
Ouch.
좋아, 도나
Okay, Donna.
우리가 널 퇴폐적이고 음란한 재미를
볼 곳으로 데려가야 되겠구나
I think we need to take you out
for some dirty bad fun.
고마워, 에릭!
Thank you, Eric.
퇴폐적이고 음란한 재미를 원해?
내가 들려주지
Oh, you want dirty bad fun?
Listen to this.
내가 올 때는 옷을 다 입고 있었거든?
I came here fully clothed--
오! 맞다. 생각났어
Ooh! No, no, no.
I know!
시카고에 새 클럽이 문을 열었는데
There's this new club
that opened in Chicago.
요새 그쪽에서 제일 잘 나간데
It's supposed to be like-- like the
hottest spot this side of Studio 54.
세상에, 거기가 딱 좋겠다!
My God, you guys, that's perfect.
아냐, 안돼 마이클
우린 거기 못가
No, no, Michael, we can't go.
우리 부모님 오늘 늦게
들어 오시거든. 그러니까..
My parents are gonna be out late tonight,
and we have to study.
우린 공부해야 돼
공부라고?
Study? Ah, what a gyp!
I'm going to the club.
싫어, 미쳤냐!
난 클럽에 갈 거야
안돼, 마이클!
No, no, Michael.
넌 오늘밤 우리집에 와야 돼
You're coming over
to my house tonight.
와서 우리 같이..
And we're gonna...
공부해야지
"study".
알았어!
Fine!
하여간 내가 재밌게 노는 꼴을
못 본다니까
God, I never get to do anything fun.
너 진짜 멍청하다
God, you're dumb.
그러니까 가서 공부나 하는 거겠지
I guess that's why
I gotta go study.
안녕하십니까? 레드 포먼입니다
노련하고, 성실하고, 근면하죠
Hi. Red Forman--
experienced, loyal, hardworking.
좋았어
Yeah.
- 여어!
- 여어, 레드 아닌가!
- Hey!
- Hey, it's Red.
공장 사람들이 여기
다 모였군 그래
It's all of you guys from
the, uh-- from the plant, huh?
우리 모두 같은 일자리를
노리고 있나 보군
So, we're all going
after the same job.
뭐, 그것 참 대단하군!
Well, that's, uh--
that's terrific.
나도 자네같은 자신감이 있었으면
좋을텐데, 난 쥐뿔도 없어
Well, I wish I had your confidence, Red.
I got nothing.
내가 내세울 거라고는 노련함과
성실성과 근면성 뿐이야
All I could think to do was tell this guy
I'm experienced, loyal and hardworking.
이런 개자식!
Son of a bitch.
책 갖고 왔어
So, I brought my books.
마이클, 우리 공부 안할거야
Michael, we're not gonna study.
안한다고?
We're not?
안해
No.
우리 부모님은
몇 시간 후에나 오실거야
My parents are gonna
be gone for hours.
아!
Oh!
그럼, 뭐하고 싶어?
So, what do you wanna do?
이것 봐, 데이빗 보위야
Oh, check it out. Bowie.
진짜 멋있다
Man, he's cool.
그래, 남녀 양성적인 남자들이
진짜 남자답다니까
Yeah, androgynous guys
are so manly.
마이클? 보위처럼 꾸미면 정말 정말
섹시할 사람이 누군지 알아?
Michael, do you know
who would look totally, totally sexy...
glammed up like Bowie?
누군데?
Who?
너야, 마이클!
You, Michael.
너 미쳤구나
You're crazy.
난 치장같은 거 안해
No, I'm not glam.
아냐, 마이클
넌 눈이 정말 예쁘단 말야
Come on, Michael.
You have such pretty eyes.
- 뭐 내 속눈썹이 열라 길긴 하지
- 그래, 맞어! 그리고
Well, my lashes do go out
like a mile. / Yeah, yeah. And..
이걸로
말아올릴 수 있어!
with this,
I can flip 'em up.
- 말도 안돼!
- 안되긴
- No way!
- Yeah, yeah!
에릭, 여기 있니?
- Eric, you here?
- Yeah, I'm in the living room, baby.
응, 나 거실에 있어, 자기야
뭘 그렇게 뚫어지게 보는거야?
What are you staring at?
너 정말..
You're really...
끝내준다
brick house.
- 고마워! 지금 갈..
- 쉬!
- Thanks. You wanna--
- Shh.
몇 초만 더 보고 있을래
Let me just stare
at you for a second.
- 그냥 좀 가면..
- 어허!
- Can we just--
- Hup.
좋아, 이제 됐어
Okay, I'm good.
이건 바보짓이야
- God, this is stupid.
- Shut up, Michael. I'm almost done.
입 다물어, 마이클!
거의 다 했단 말야
나한테 이 짓을 하게 내버려 두다니
I can't believe I let you
talk me into this.
됐다, 한 번 봐봐
Okay. Here. Take a look.
그래, 진짜 이쁘긴 하다
Okay, yeah,
my eyes are gorgeous.
그것봐! 내 말이 맞지
See? See? I told you.
마이클, 여기다 뭘 더 해야 될지 알아?
Michael, do you know
what you need now? Some blush.
볼터치!
오! 오! 오! 재키!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Jackie.
눈화장한 것 까지는 좋았어
그치만 더하면 정말 이상해질 거야
All right, glam is one thing,
but I think we're crossing over into weird.
No, no, trust me, Michael,
we're not.
아냐, 날 믿어 마이클
하나도 안 이상하다니까
너 같은 광대뼈엔
볼터치가 딱 어울린다고
With cheekbones like that,
blush is your best friend.
Yeah, I do have
bitchin' cheekbones.
내 광대뼈가 근사하긴 하지
좋아, 볼터치도 하자!
Okay, let's blush!
이 동네 사람들 정말 친절하다!
People are so friendly
around here.
모퉁이에 있던 여자 둘이
나한테 섹스하자고 했어
Two women on the corner
just offered to have sex with me.
돈 때문에 그런거야, 페즈
Yeah. For money, Fez.
내가 그 여자들한테
돈까지 달라고 할 수는 없지!
I could not ask them
for money.
그래도 되나?
Or could I?
와, 이 많은 사람들 좀 봐!
Wow, guys.
Check out this crowd.
그러게, 끝내주게 재미있을 거야
얼마나 기다려야 되는지 알아보자
I know. This is gonna be so great!
Let's go see how long the wait is.
- 실례지만, 얼마나 기다려야...
- 들어가쇼!
- Excuse me, how long--
- You're in.
야, 너무 잘 됐다
Oh, man, I'm so up for this.
니들은 안돼
Not you.
괜찮아, 여기서 같이 기다려줄게
Well, that's fine.
I'll just wait with you guys.
- 아냐, 바로 다음인데, 먼저 들어가
- 그럴까?
- No, we're next. Go in.
- Yeah?
알았어, 그럼 안에서 보자
All right,
I'll see you guys inside.
이게 아마 소방법 때문에
인원제한이 있어서 그러는 걸 거야
You know what? This is probably
just some kind of fire code thing.
잠깐요, 왜 그러세요?
우리 차례잖아요
Yeah, okay. Wait.
What's going on? We're next.
아니야, 니들 차례 아니야
No. You're not.
무슨 말을 하는 거예요?
What are you talking about?
Well, Archie...
꼬마야
킹카는 들여보내고
폭탄은 걸러내는 게 내 일이야
I'm here to let the cool people
in and keep the geeks out.
저 불쌍한 폭탄들!
Those poor stupid geeks!
에게? 우리가 폭탄이란 거잖아!
Oh, my God.
We are geeks.
경비원 몰래 들어가는 거 성공했냐?
Hey, did slipping
the bouncer a ten work?
그래, 성공했어 하이드
그래서 내가 지금 클럽 안에 있잖냐
Yes, it did, Hyde.
That's why I'm inside the club.
거기 있었구나!
There you are.
여기 정말 끝내줘!
왜 안 들어와?
This place is awesome.
Why aren't you inside?
어, 들어갔었는데..
안에 있었는데..
Oh, we were in.
We were on the inside.
- 난 못 봤는데
- 너한테 손 흔들었었는데
- I didn't see you.
- Oh, yeah, we waved at you.
근데 너 그 때..
But you were, uh--
- Dancing.
- Excellent.
- 춤추고 있었어
- 바로 그거야!
니가 춤추고 있더라구
그래서 우리가 간 곳이..
Uh, you were dancing.
And then we went through this--
- 문
- 맞어, 문밖으로 나왔어
- Door.
- Yes. We went through this door.
근데 곧바로는 다시
못 들어가게 하더라고
And we were locked out.
그래서 맨 뒷줄로 다시 서게 됐어
And then we had to get in
the back of the line, so--
알았어, 그럼 다시
들어오면 날 찾아
When you get back inside,
find me.
- 알았어, 들어가
- 어서 들어가
- Go. Yeah.
- Yeah.
- 좀 있다 안에서 보자
- 알았어
- We'll meet you on the inside.
- Okay.
- 들어가
- 가라
- You go.
- Go.
잘도 둘러치는구나
That was really smooth.
잘했으니까 들어가도 돼요?
Smooth enough to get us in?
아니
No.
Okay, that's it.
You must take me in.
더 이상 못참아!
나 꼭 들여보내줘야 해요!
왜?
Why?
내 사타구니 안에서 디스코
리듬이 불타고 있단 말이에요
Because I feel the hot rhythm
of disco burning in my loins.
Watch.
보세요
좋아, 넌 들어가
Okay, you're in.
잘 있어라, 한심한 것들아
So long, losers!
이게 진짜 안 떨어진단 말이야?
You're saying that this stuff
won't come off?
울어도?
Like even if I cry?
와, 정말 굉장하다
Man, that's great.
마이클, 넌 지금껏 내가
가진 인형 중에 최고야
Oh, Michael, you are the best doll
I have ever had.
맞다, 너한테 딱
맞는 드레스도 있어
You know what?
I have the perfect gown for you.
잠깐, 재키. 살살해
All right, Jackie.
Slow down.
립스틱 바르는 것까지는 봐주는데
Okay, wearing lipstick
is one thing...
드레스라니?
but a gown,
that's kind of fruity.
그건 호모나 하는 짓이잖아
아냐, 아냐, 마이클!
No, no, it's not, Michael.
데이빗 보위도 입는단 말이야!
Bowie wears dresses.
Joe Namath wears panty hose.
조 네이미스는 팬티 스타킹도 신고!
미남 인기 미식축구선수
재키, 싫어!
Jackie, no.
금방 가져올게
I'll be right back.
재키, 싫다니까!
Jackie, I said, "No!"
좋아, 너무 계집애같은 건 안돼
이건 정말이야
All right, nothing too girlie.
And I mean it!
너의 그 '한번에 둘은 못 잡는다'
이론이 잘도 통하는구나
Well, so much for your
"He can't stop both of us" theory.
정말 짜증나!
이건 말도 안돼
This bites, man!
He can't keep us out of there.
이게 뭐야..
여기가 무슨 러시아야?
I mean, what--
Did we wake up in Russia this morning?
아니
No.
여기가 러시아가 아닌건 확실해!
We did not, in fact,
wake up in Russia this morning!
내 말이 바로 그거야!
I didn't think so!
이봐, 내 말 잘 들어, 형씨!
Hey, let me tell you something, pal.
You're propping up a dying system, man.
당신 한물간 시스템을 따르고 있는거야
사람들은 조만간 깨닫게 될거라고
'Cause, see, some day soon,
people are gonna wake up...
당신네 그 헐리웃이나
매디슨 에비뉴같이 근사한 곳엔
and they're gonna realize
that most of us don't fit into your...
자신들이 발 딛을 틈이
없다는 걸 알게 될 거고
Hollywood, Madison Avenue,
candy-coated ideal of what's cool.
그럼 우린 반기를
들고 일어날 거야!
And when we do,
we're gonna rise up.
그땐 당신을 심판대에 올리겠어!
We're gonna put you on trial,
당신 머리를 장대에 매달고
거리를 행진할 거라고!
then parade through the streets
with your head on a stick!
정당한 정치적 분노로군
넌 들어가라
Righteous political outrage.
You're in.
좋았어!
나중에 보자, 포먼
All right.
I'll see ya later, Forman.
그래요, 그게
Yeah, well...
혁명이 시작되면요, 형씨
when the revolution comes, man...
아저씨를 벽에 매달 거예요
your back's gonna be
up against the wall--
제기랄, 들여보내 줘요!
내 여자친구가 안에 있다구요!
Damn it, let me in!
My girlfriend's in there!
그 빨간머리에 섹시한 애?
난 네 누난줄 알았는데
The foxy redhead?
I thought that was your sister.
뭘 보고 너같은 애랑
사귀고 있다냐?
What does she see in you?
뭘 보고 나랑 사귀냐구요?
You know what she sees, buddy?
그게 알고 싶어요?
You know what she sees?
좋아요, 한 마디만 하죠
만약 도나가 경비원이었으면
Well, let me tell you something.
If she was the bouncer...
저 바보같은 클럽 안에 들여보내
줬을 거예요, 이 얼간아!
I'd be in that stupid club
right now, you big ass.
그래요
Yeah,
알았죠?
I said it.
나 왔어요, 여보
Hi, honey.
저런
Uh-oh.
그 일자리 못 얻었어
I didn't get the job.
괜찮아요, 다음번엔 잘 될 거예요
Okay, well, you will get
them next time.
흠, 여보
Ah, Kitty...
세상이 바뀌고 있어
the world's changin'.
내가 기대하던 대로
돼가는 것 같지 않아
Things aren't turning out
the way I expected.
여보, 당신이 기대하던 게 뭔데요?
Well, Red, what did you expect?
글쎄
Well,
나도 잘 모르겠어
I don't know.
이걸 받아라, 히로히토!
2차대전 당시 일왕
Take that, Hirohito.
그걸로 끝이다!
And that.
바다 건너에서 완벽한 승리를 쟁취한
Yes, with America's victory
overseas now complete...
우리의 용사들이 집으로 돌아옵니다
our fighting boys return home...
미국의 근로자들이
where the American workingman...
정당한 주권을 행사할 수 있는 곳이죠
takes his rightful place on the throne.
"어서와요, 여보!
오늘 어땠어요?"
"Hi, honey.
How was your day?"
"또 월급을 올려주더군"
"They gave me another raise."
"여보, 당신이 버는 그 많은 돈 덕에
"Oh, honey.
With all the money you make...
나는 일할 필요가 전혀 없어요"
it's no wonder
I don't have to work."
딸 로리가 질문을 합니다
Daughter Laurie
has a question.
"아빠, 다른 나라에서 왜
미국의 경제를 선망하는거죠?"
"Daddy, why is the American
economy the envy of the world?"
"그건.."
아버지가 대답합니다
"Well," says Dad...
"미국의 일꾼들이 숙련되고
"it's because the American
worker is experienced...
성실하며, 근면하기 때문이란다"
loyal and hardworking."
아들에게 좋은 소식이 있는 것 같군요
Looks like Junior
has some good news.
"아버지, 이제 더이상
제게 돈을 안주셔도 돼요"
"Say, Dad, you can stop
giving me money now.
"노틀담에서 제게 축구
장학금을 주기로 했거든요!"
"I just got a football
scholarship to Notre Dame.
"경험, 성실성, 근면성을
키운 보람이 있는 것 같아요! "
"I guess experience,
loyalty...
and hard work
really do pay off."
딸 로리가 또 질문을 합니다
Daughter Laurie
has another question.
"아빠, 독일과 일본의 경제가 전혀
회복되지 않은 이유가 뭔가요?"
"Daddy, can you tell me why Germany
and Japan 's economies never recovered?"
"간단하지"
"It's simple.
"그들은 숙련되지도 않았고
They are not experienced.
근면하지도 않고
"They are not hardworking.
성실하지도 않기 때문이야"
"They are not loyal.
"게다가 영어도 못 하거든"
And they do not speak English."
"일 얘기가 나왔으니 말인데요
엄마 식료품 사러 가야 된데요"
Speaking of work,
Mom has to go grocery shopping.
"캐딜락 키 좀 줄래요?"
"Can I have the keys
to the Cadillac?"
"하하! 캐딜락은 잊으라구!
호버크래프트를 타고 갔다와"
수륙 양용차
"Forget the Cadillac!
Take the hovercraft."
"여보. 호버크래프트라구요?"
"Red, the hovercraft?"
호버크래프트요?
The hovercraft?
왜?
What?
제대하면 그거 준다고 약속했었어
They promised us
hovercrafts.
지켜지지 않은 또 하나의
약속일 뿐이지만 말이야
It's just another
damn broken promise.
여기요, 프림 하나, 설탕 둘
Okay. Cream. Two sugars.
이제 그거 마셨으니
들여보내 줄거죠?
Well, you just drink up and
I'll just-- I don't know-- head inside.
그래
- Yeah. No.
- Oh, come on! You suck!
- 안돼
- 제발요, 너무 해요
거물 경비원 나리!
'내가 열고 닫지' 나리!
Mr. Big Shot Bouncer,
Mr. I Open and Close the Rope...
스틱스 강의 뱃사공 나리
죽은 자가 건너야 하는 지하세계의 강
Mr. Boatman on the River Styx.
제기랄! 당신은 살면서 한번도 뭔가에서
제외 당해본 적 없나 보죠?
Just-- God, I bet you've never been excluded
from anything in your whole life!
이봐! 그렇지 않아
나도 여러번 왕따 당해봤다고
Hey, that's not fair!
I've been excluded from lots of things.
그래요, 예를 들면요?
Yeah, like what?
아 그래, 맞아
내가 유치원다닐 때
Oh, no, okay.
Uh, when I was in kindergarten...
수건돌리기하며 놀곤 했었거든
we used to play
Duck, Duck, Goose...
근데 아무도 날 술래로
뽑아준 적이 없었어
and nobody ever picked me
to be the goose.
와, 굉장히 상처가 컸겠군요
Oh, wow.
That must have really hurt.
별로 신경 안 썼어
I didn't care.
신경을 안 썼다고요?
You didn't care? Uh-huh.
아이들이 동그랗게
둘러앉아 노래를 부르고
So you were just sitting there,
watching this kid go around the circle.
원을 돌던 술래가
조금씩 나랑 가까워지면
Duck. Duck. Duck.
He'd get closer and closer.
기대감에 떨게 되죠
Duck. You'd be shaking
with anticipation.
어쩌면 날 뽑아줄지도 몰라
Duck. Maybe he'll pick me. Duck.
그럼 '술래가 되어 신나게 수건을 갖고
돌텐데'라고 기대에 부풀어 있을 때
Maybe I'll get to run and laugh
with the joy of being the goose.
아저씨 바로 뒤를
그냥 지나가 버리는데
Then he'd come to you, place his hand
on your head, and say, "Duck."
- 아저씬, 신경 안 썼다구요?
- 그래, 생각해보니 가슴 아프군
- And you're telling me you didn't care?
- Yeah, it hurts.
네, 그게.. 고마워요!
제말이 바로 그거예요!
Yes, it-- Thank you!
That's what I'm saying!
이번엔, 아저씨가 저를
And now,
you have made me...
술래 안 시키고 계세요!
the duck.
Wow.
네 기분이 그럴 줄은 몰랐다
Oh, man, I didn't realize.
가서 춤 추고 놀거라, 술래야
Dance, goose, dance.
마이클, 그 드레스 입으니까
데이빗 보위보다 훨씬 예쁘다!
Oh, God, Michael. In that dress,
you are way prettier than Bowie.
그뿐이겠어?
내가 너보다도 예쁘다고!
Hell, I'm prettier than you.
재미없어, 마이클
That's not funny, Michael.
차 멈추는 소리 못 들었니?
Did you just hear a car pull up?
진정해, 재키, 너희 부모님
오시려면 몇 시간 남았잖아
Relax, Jackie, your parents aren't supposed
to be home for, like, another hour.
나 돌려줘
Now, spin me.
- 아빠 오셨어요?
- 공부하고 있었어요
- Hi, Daddy.
- We're studying.
안돼요, 아빠
내가 사랑하는 애에요!
No, no. Daddy, no! Daddy, I love him.
- 멋진 밤이었어, 그치?
- 음, 그래
- Wow. What a night, right?
- Oh, exactly.
도나, 나랑 왜 사귀는 거야?
Donna, why are you with me?
경비원 아저씨가 궁금해 하더라
Um, the bouncer
wanted to know.
그래서 뭐라고 그랬는데?
What'd you tell him?
사실은, 나도 모르겠더라고
You know, I couldn't
think of a reason.
흠
Hmm.
생각해보니까
나도 잘 모르겠다
You know, come to think of it,
I can't either.
너랑은 전혀 다른 사람을
찾아볼 필요가 있겠어
What I need to do is find a guy
who's like totally different from you.
덩치도 크고, 바보같고
날 함부로 대하는 놈으로
Maybe big, and dumb,
and, you know, not nice to me.
그리고 유머감각도 없어서
내가 농담해도 안 웃는 인간 말야
Oh, and no sense of humor,
so when I tell a joke, he doesn't get it.
- 그럼 나 진짜 흥분될 거야
- 알았어, 됐어
- I mean, that's a real turn on.
- Okay, enough.
아냐, 아냐, 진심이야
정말 고마워
No, no, no, seriously,
thank you.
네가 지적해 주지 않았으면
너한테 몇 년을 허비할 뻔했잖아
I mean, if you hadn't pointed this out to me,
I might have wasted years with you.
너랑 섹스도 할 뻔 했단 말야
I mean, I almost
had sex with you.
우와! 고마워
Whoo! Thank you.
이제는 왜 내가 너랑
사귀는지가 궁금해진다
Okay, I think the question
has become, why am I with you?
그래, 알았어
Oh, right. Okay.
정말 즐거운 시간이었어
I had a great time.
잘 자
Good night.
그렇다니까
Yeah.
어젯밤은 재키랑 보냈고
Last night I was with Jackie.
오늘밤은 로리랑 보낼 거야
Tonight, I'll be with Laurie.
이런게 바로 나같은
변강쇠님의 삶 아니겠냐
That's just the kind of life
that a stud like me leads.
왜?
What?
켈소, 너 마스카라 흘러 내린다
Kelso, your mascara's running.
젠장!
Damn!
재키가 물에 안 번진댔는데
She told me it was waterproof.
번역수정 : 강효진(cheeeeese@nate.com)
한글교정 : 김찬미 (husseyttl@nate)
최종수정 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24